datso.fr 2012-10-30

# Privacy Policy

DATSO.FR is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to the web site DATSO.FR, which governs data collection and usage. By using DATSO.FR, you agree to the data practices described in this statement. 

Collection of your Personal Information

DATSO.FR collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by DATSO.FR. This information can include: your IP-address, browser type, access times and website addresses. This information is used by DATSO.FR for operation of the service, to maintain quality of service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the web site DATSO.FR.

DATSO.FR encourages you to review the privacy statements of web sites you choose to link to DATSO.FR so that you can understand how those web sites collect, use and share your information. DATSO.FR not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside DATSO.FR and DATSO.FR family of web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

DATSO.FR collects and uses your personal information to operate the DATSO.FR, and deliver the services you have requested. DATSO.FR also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DATSO.FR.

DATSO.FR does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

DATSO.FR does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

DATSO.FR web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DATSO.FR or the site
  * protect and defend the rights or property of DATSO.FR
  * act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DATSO.FR, or the public

Changes to this Statement

DATSO.FR will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DATSO.FR encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DATSO.FR is protecting your information.

Contact Information

DATSO.FR welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DATSO.FR has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DATSO.FR at [support@datso.fr](mailto:support@datso.fr) We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
